rufftv.com 2015-03-15

# RuffTV

## Privacy Policy

General

RuffTV is committed to protecting your privacy when you use the RuffTV website. This Privacy Policy informs you of the types of information RuffTV collects about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom RuffTV discloses it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. Please read carefully.

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All data is protected using the most advanced methods available. In addition to the information you provide through our order-form, we may store the following pieces of data: IP address, times when connected to our service, and the total amount of data transfered per day. We store this to be able to deliver the best possible network experience to you. We keep this information secure and private. If we receive complaints regarding copyrighted materials such as music and movies being shared over our network, we may filter traffic to see which account is sending it, and then cancel that account. We do not as a matter of ordinary practice store private information about individual user activities on our network, such as emails, chats, VOIP calls, websites visited, etc. However, should we receive a valid request from US law enforcement officials, we may be forced to comply, even with no warning to the user.

Collection of Information

RuffTV may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding your use of the RuffTV website. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of the RuffTV website's user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by RuffTV and other third-party advertising providers during your use of the RuffTV website and in serving advertisements to the RuffTV website.

RuffTV may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on the RuffTV website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that the RuffTV website places onto the user's computer hard drive. Cookies identify the user's computer hard drive so that the RuffTV website can recognize you the next time you visit.

Third party advertisements displayed on or in connection with the RuffTV website may also contain cookies set by such advertisers. RuffTV does not control these cookies and users of the RuffTV website should check the privacy policy of such advertisers to understand whether and how it uses cookies.

Use of Information

If you submit personally identifiable information to RuffTV through the RuffTV website, then RuffTV may use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the site.

RuffTV does not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. RuffTV may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes

Disclosure of Information

RuffTV may share aggregated statistical information and profile information about users of the RuffTV website with third-parties, including distributors, vendors, advertisers actual and potential customers and business partners. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

RuffTV will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

RuffTV may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

RuffTV also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that, in good faith, if appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the RuffTV website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of RuffTV, our users or others.

Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice

This privacy notice may be revised periodically and users are encouraged to review it periodically to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the RuffTV website constitutes your agreement to this privacy notice and any future revisions.
